<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Taylor Contreras</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Taylor Contreras</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Book Talk</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/05/book-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/05/book-talk/</guid>
      <description>Like nearly everyone on the planet, I had a New Year’s resolution. I wanted to read more books. I have loved reading for as long as I can remember. Yet, I think the last time I had really read more than the books assigned for school was my sophomore year of high school. I got busy applying for college and getting jobs. It didn’t bother me until I was trapped at home every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python </title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/05/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/05/python/</guid>
      <description>I talk about Python here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project #1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this project I will be looking at two datasets.
I found these two datasets on a website listing R datasets (https://vincentarelbundock.github.io/Rdatasets/datasets.html). The first dataset looks at the number of teen pregnancies per 1000 girls in each U.S. state, the state’s role in the Civil War, and the percentage of the state who attended church in the previous week. The second dataset looks at each U.S. state, the expenditure per pupil in average daily attendance, the student to teacher ratio, the teacher salary, the percentage of all eligible student taking the SAT, the average verbal SAT score, the average math SAT score and the average overall SAT score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project #2</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this project I will be looking at some Extramarital affairs data. I found this data from the website listing various R datasets: https://vincentarelbundock.github.io/Rdatasets/datasets.html. My dataset includes the following variables: sex, age, number of years married, if there are children, a scale of how religious they are, education, economic statues according to Hollingshead’s classification, a rating of happiness on the marriage, and the number of affairs in the past year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
